<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://totallynotgoingtobescammed.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://totallynotgoingtobescammed.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-03-14T20:56:09+00:00</updated><id>https://totallynotgoingtobescammed.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ностальгия</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">DDoS Attacks</title><link href="https://totallynotgoingtobescammed.github.io/blog/2022/attack/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="DDoS Attacks" /><published>2022-01-19T21:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-01-19T21:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://totallynotgoingtobescammed.github.io/blog/2022/attack</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://totallynotgoingtobescammed.github.io/blog/2022/attack/"><![CDATA[<p>Browsing websites is easy. But when you are in the middle of a search, you get interrupted by a screen that is asking you the easiest question. You sigh and continue.</p>

<p>Usually people don’t put it on their mind and usually don’t care. But have you ever wondered why it’s there? Well that is what prevents DDOS attacks.</p>

<p>DDOS attacks are really annoying for other people. It jams other people’s devices and basically breaks the website. It’s like a narrow road with too many cars or vehicles.</p>

<p>This is why we have reCAPTCHA. reCAPTCHA is a system that asks you to complete a set of simple questions. This is used to block bots so that it can block DDOS attacks.</p>

<p>reCAPTCHA is sometimes really helpful but not really efficient. Let’s say you are on your way to an urgent meeting and you are really stressed out because you are almost late. But then reCAPTCHA comes out of nowhere. Because of your stress you didn’t do it correctly. So then you got banned. After that, your boss fired you and now you are broke.</p>

<p>In the future, reCAPTCHA should update its system and be able to block hackers and also be a lot more efficient.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some random complaints on reCaptcha.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Youtubers</title><link href="https://totallynotgoingtobescammed.github.io/blog/2021/youtubers/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Youtubers" /><published>2021-12-11T21:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-12-11T21:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://totallynotgoingtobescammed.github.io/blog/2021/youtubers</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://totallynotgoingtobescammed.github.io/blog/2021/youtubers/"><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever wondered how some youtubers that you think are boring have so many subscribers? Well that is true because that is what a lot of people like these days. Young kids think it is fun because that is what their minds are like. They are attracted to these types of genres, like video games and destruction. Some who are factual like videos about maybe space or coding or DIY builds. It usually depends on what that person likes.</p>

<p>Some youtubers capture most of the things kids like, like MrBeast. He almost captures all the genres kids enjoy. He has videos of gameplay, donations, survival, and probably more. Also sometimes you can talk about how your life is. I am a big fan of TheOdd1sOut. It talks about a kid talking about his life. It is very interesting because I really like how he talks all about his life and the events that happened in it. It really makes me laugh when he talks about the funny events. That is something very good that youtubers do. Sometimes, it also depends on the games they play. If they play a popular game, then they probably would get a lot of subscribers. They also need to be good at the game, that is really important. If you aren’t good at the game. People would think it is a waste of time and would probably even dislike the video. So it really depends on their skill and experience.</p>

<p>Well that is really how they get subscribers. If the youtuber you think is boring and has a lot of subscribers that don’t follow the steps, then they must have some different ideas. If you look at MarkRober, he kind of falls in the DIY section or coding section. Also Dream and Technoblade, they all fall in the gaming section. They all play Minecraft and are really good at it. That is also why they get a lot of subscribers. Now you know how youtubers get subscribers you can start your own! You can talk about anything in this list and you can probably become a great youtuber!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Random Thoughts on Youtubers.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Immune</title><link href="https://totallynotgoingtobescammed.github.io/blog/2021/immune/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Immune" /><published>2021-11-23T21:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-11-23T21:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://totallynotgoingtobescammed.github.io/blog/2021/immune</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://totallynotgoingtobescammed.github.io/blog/2021/immune/"><![CDATA[<p>You wake up with a headache and a sore throat and are getting ready for school. While you are waking up or brushing your teeth, deep in your body, there is a war raging on. The war is between your cells and group A Streptococcus or other viruses. This war is a very gruesome war. The immune system is very strategic in battle.</p>

<div class="row mt-3">
    <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0">
        <img class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" src="/assets/img/pAbacteria.jpeg" width="200" height="200" />
    </div>
    <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0">
        <img class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" src="/assets/img/groupa-strep.jpg" width="200" height="200" />
    </div>
</div>
<div class="caption">
    Viruses. They are bad.
</div>

<p>First is your Innate immune system. You were born with this immune system. It protects your weak organs from viruses in early life. It also is helpful on the battlefield. The next bit is your Adaptive immune system. It is developed while you grow. Here is the first line of defense.</p>

<p>First of all the barrier-like cells is your skin cells. It helps prevent any virus from coming in. Well unless there is a cut. Let’s say you got cut by a rusty nail. The part would start bulging and bleeding because your blood is trying to heal the cut. Well while the red blood cells are trying to heal your outside cut. Little sneaky germs are coming in. These  sneaky germs adapt and camouflage by turning the same color as the red blood cells so the white blood cells won’t find them. But some couldn’t camouflage fast enough and got eaten by the white blood cells.</p>

<p>You might be asking, how do they camouflage? Do they have eyes to see? No, they don’t have any eyes at all. But they have a way. By using protein. Using protein will help them blend in and camouflage by recognizing their surroundings. But here is the problem. They can’t hide forever. You see, your immune system has little receptors on its side that make it able to detect different proteins. While the bacteria look the same and it is hard to see the difference, they don’t have the exact same bit of protein. A few bits are still bacteria protein. So the immune system can track them down and kill them.</p>

<p>Even though you might just drink some hot water and continue your day. Deep in your body is a huge war between two enemies.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Journey into the Mysterious System That Keeps You Alive.]]></summary></entry></feed>